Ah, thank you.
谢了
Hey. That's our last apple.
那是我们最后一个苹果
Then why are you using it for target practice?
那你为什么拿它当靶子练习
I use these breaks to stay sharp.
我利用休息时间保持敏锐
Good. Stay sharp with your own apples.
很好 用你自己的苹果保持敏锐吧
I'm sorry, but shouldn't the concern here be that someone was about to shoot an apple off my head?!
不好意思 但是重点难道不是有人要在我头上射苹果吗
Lance, that's our last apple.
兰斯 那是我们最后一个苹果
Then someone got here just in time.
那我来的真凑巧
Apple usurper!
苹果簒夺者
I want my apple back.
我要拿回我的苹果
Don't think just because you got horse slobber all over it, I'm not still gonna eat it.
不要以为上面沾满马的口水 我就不会吃了
It's about principle now.
现在是原则问题
Uh-oh, Pascal. Sounds like another apple brawl.
帕斯考 听起来他们又在为抢苹果吵架了